Guide to the Red Lodge Canning Company Records 1922-1974
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Correspondence, 1924-1974; Series I; 58.25 linear feet
  - General Correspondence, 1924-1974; Subseries 1; 56.0 linear feet
    - American Can Company, 1938 (Box-folder 36/4)
    - A, 1938 (Box-folder 36/5)
    - B, 1938 (Box-folder 36/6)
    - C, 1938 (Box-folder 36/7)
    - D, 1938 (Box-folder 36/8)
    - E, 1938 (Box-folder 36/9)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1938 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - F, 1938 (Box-folder 37/2)
    - G, 1938 (Box-folder 37/3)
    - H-I, 1938 (Box-folder 37/4)
    - K, 1938 (Box-folder 37/5)
    - T. J. Lanphier Company, 1938 (Box-folder 37/6)
    - T. J. Lanphier Company, 1938 (Box-folder 37/7)
    - Lansing B. Warner Incorporated, 1938 (Box-folder 37/8)
    - L, 1938 (Box-folder 37/9)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1938 (Box-folder 37/10)
    - Meinrath Brokerage Company, 1938 (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Midland National Bank, 1938 (Box-folder 38/2)
    - Miles City Mercantile Company, 1938 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - Missoula Mercantile Company, 1938 (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Montana, 1938 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Morrison Brothers Seed Company, 1938 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - Muirson Label Company, 1938 (Box-folder 38/7)
    - M, 1938 (Box-folder 38/8)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1938 (Box-folder 38/9)
    - National Canners Association, 1938 (Box-folder 38/10)
    - N, 1938 (Box-folder 38/11)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1938 (Box-folder 38/12)
    - O-P, 1938 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Ryan Grocery Company, 1938 (Box-folder 39/2)
    - R, 1938 (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1938 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - S, 1938 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - T, 1938 (Box-folder 39/6)
    - U.S. Government, 1938 (Box-folder 39/7)
    - U.S. Printing and Lithograph Company, 1938 (Box-folder 39/8)
    - Western States Grocery Company, 1938 (Box-folder 39/9)
    - U-W, 1938 (Box-folder 39/10)
    - Allen Brokerage Company, 1939 (Box-folder 39/11)
    - American Can Company, 1939 (Box-folder 39/12)
    - Associated Seed Growers Association, 1939 (Box-folder 39/13)
    - A, 1939 (Box-folder 40/1)
    - B, 1939 (Box-folder 40/2)
    - Canned Pea Marketing Cooperation, 1939 (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Curtis Lighting, 1939 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - C, 1939 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - D, 1939 (Box-folder 40/6)
    - E, 1939 (Box-folder 40/7)
    - James Fenwick Company, 1939 (Box-folder 40/8)
    - Foley Brokerage Company, 1939 (Box-folder 40/9)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1939 (Box-folder 40/10)
    - F, 1939 (Box-folder 40/11)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1939 (Box-folder 40/12)
    - G, 1939 (Box-folder 40/13)
    - H, 1939 (Box-folder 40/14)
    - I, 1939 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Kalispell Grocery, 1939 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - K, 1939 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - L, 1939 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1939 (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Meinrath Brokerage Company, 1939 (Box-folder 41/6)
    - Miles City Mercantile, 1939 (Box-folder 41/7)
    - Missoula Mercantile Company, 1939 (Box-folder 41/8)
    - Montana, 1939 (Box-folder 41/9)
    - M, 1939 (Box-folder 41/10)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1939 (Box-folder 41/11)
    - N, 1939 (Box-folder 42/1)
    - O, 1939 (Box-folder 42/2)
    - P, 1939 (Box-folder 42/3)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1939 (Box-folder 42/4)
    - Ryan Grocery Company and Subsidiaries, 1939 (Box-folder 42/5)
    - R, 1939 (Box-folder 42/6)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1939 (Box-folder 42/7)
    - S, 1939 (Box-folder 42/8)
    - United States Government, 1939 (Box-folder 42/9)
    - T-V, 1939 (Box-folder 42/10)
    - Lansing B. Warner Incorporated, 1939 (Box-folder 42/11)
    - Western States Grocery Company, 1939 (Box-folder 42/12)
    - W-Z, 1939 (Box-folder 42/13)
    - Allen Brokerage Company, 1940 (Box-folder 43/1)
    - American Can Company, 1940 (Box-folder 43/2)
    - Association Seed Growers Incorporated, 1940 (Box-folder 43/3)
    - A, 1940 (Box-folder 43/4)
    - Big Horn Canning Company, 1940 (Box-folder 43/5)
    - Billings Grocery Company, 1940 (Box-folder 43/6)
    - Bismarck Grocery Company, 1940 (Box-folder 43/7)
    - Bowler Brokerage Company, 1940 (Box-folder 43/8)
    - B, 1940 (Box-folder 43/9)
    - Central Grocery Company, 1940 (Box-folder 43/10)
    - Cooter Brokerage Company, 1940 (Box-folder 43/11)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1940 (Box-folder 43/12)
    - C, 1940 (Box-folder 44/1)
    - D, 1940 (Box-folder 44/2)
    - E, 1940 (Box-folder 44/3)
    - Foley Brokerage Company, 1940 (Box-folder 44/4)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1940 (Box-folder 44/5)
    - F, 1940 (Box-folder 44/6)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1940 (Box-folder 44/7)
    - George W. Goddard Company, 1940 (Box-folder 44/8)
    - Harold B. Godfrey, 1940 (Box-folder 44/9)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1940 (Box-folder 44/10)
    - G, 1940 (Box-folder 44/11)
    - H, 1940 (Box-folder 44/12)
    - I, 1940 (Box-folder 44/13)
    - J, 1940 (Box-folder 44/14)
    - Kalispell Grocery Company, 1940 (Box-folder 44/15)
    - Keil Company, 1940 (Box-folder 44/16)
    - Kelly-How-Thompson Company, 1940 (Box-folder 44/17)
    - K, 1940 (Box-folder 44/18)
    - James Q. Leavitt, 1940 (Box-folder 45/1)
    - L, 1940 (Box-folder 45/2)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1940 (Box-folder 45/3)
    - Meinrath Brokerage Company, 1940 (Box-folder 45/4)
    - Miles City Mercantile Company, 1940 (Box-folder 45/5)
    - Missoula Mercantile Company, 1940 (Box-folder 45/6)
    - Montana, 1940 (Box-folder 45/7)
    - M, 1940 (Box-folder 45/8)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1940 (Box-folder 45/9)
    - National Canners Association, 1940 (Box-folder 45/10)
    - Northern Pacific Railway Company, 1940 (Box-folder 45/11)
    - N, 1940 (Box-folder 46/1)
    - O, 1940 (Box-folder 46/2)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1940 (Box-folder 46/3)
    - P, 1940 (Box-folder 46/4)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1940 (Box-folder 46/5)
    - Ryan Wholesale Grocery, 1940 (Box-folder 46/6)
    - R, 1940 (Box-folder 46/7)
    - Safeway Stores Incorporated, 1940 (Box-folder 46/8)
    - Alden Smith Brokerage, 1940 (Box-folder 46/9)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1940 (Box-folder 46/10)
    - S, 1940 (Box-folder 46/11)
    - Triangle Brokerage Company, 1940 (Box-folder 47/1)
    - T, 1940 (Box-folder 47/2)
    - United States, 1940 (Box-folder 47/3)
    - United States Printing and Lithograph Company, 1940 (Box-folder 47/4)
    - U, 1940 (Box-folder 47/5)
    - V, 1940 (Box-folder 47/6)
    - Lansing B. Warner Incorporated, 1940 (Box-folder 47/7)
    - Western States Grocery Company, 1940 (Box-folder 47/8)
    - W, 1940 (Box-folder 47/9)
    - Y, 1940 (Box-folder 47/10)
    - Allen Brokerage Company, 1940 (Box-folder 47/11)
    - American Can Company, 1941 (Box-folder 47/12)
    - Association Growers Incorporated, 1941 (Box-folder 47/13)
    - A, 1941 (Box-folder 47/14)
    - Bowler Brokerage Company, 1941 (Box-folder 47/15)
    - B, 1941 (Box-folder 47/16)
    - Calvert Lithographing Company, 1941 (Box-folder 48/1)
    - Carpenter Paper Company, 1941 (Box-folder 48/2)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1941 (Box-folder 48/3)
    - C, 1941 (Box-folder 48/4)
    - Donations, 1941 (Box-folder 48/5)
    - D, 1941 (Box-folder 48/6)
    - Epsen Lithograph Company, 1941 (Box-folder 48/7)
    - E, 1941 (Box-folder 48/8)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1941 (Box-folder 48/9)
    - F, 1941 (Box-folder 48/10)
    - G, 1941 (Box-folder 48/11)
    - A. A. Hallander Company, 1941 (Box-folder 48/12)
    - H, 1941 (Box-folder 48/13)
    - I, 1941 (Box-folder 48/14)
    - K, 1941 (Box-folder 48/15)
    - L, 1941 (Box-folder 48/16)
    - McGill Colortype Company, 1941 (Box-folder 48/17)
    - Meinrath Brokerage, 1941 (Box-folder 48/18)
    - Missoula Mercantile Company, 1941 (Box-folder 49/1)
    - Montana, 1941 (Box-folder 49/2)
    - VOID, 1941 (Box-folder 49/3)
    - M, 1941 (Box-folder 49/4)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1941 (Box-folder 49/5)
    - N, 1941 (Box-folder 49/6)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1941 (Box-folder 49/7)
    - O, 1941 (Box-folder 49/8)
    - P, 1941 (Box-folder 49/9)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1941 (Box-folder 49/10)
    - Rogers Brothers Seed Company, 1941 (Box-folder 49/11)
    - Ryan Wholesale Groceries Company, 1941 (Box-folder 49/12)
    - R, 1941 (Box-folder 49/13)
    - Safeway Stores, 1941 (Box-folder 49/14)
    - Alden Smith Brokerage, 1941 (Box-folder 49/15)
    - Stone-Hall Company, 1941 (Box-folder 50/1)
    - S, 1941 (Box-folder 50/2)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1941 (Box-folder 50/3)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1941 (Box-folder 50/4)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1941 (Box-folder 50/5)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1941 (Box-folder 50/6)
    - T, 1941 (Box-folder 50/7)
    - United States, 1941 (Box-folder 51/1)
    - United States Military Depot Quartermaster, 1941 (Box-folder 51/2)
    - United States Military Depot Quartermaster, 1941 (Box-folder 51/3)
    - United States Printing and Lithograph Company, 1941 (Box-folder 51/4)
    - U, 1941 (Box-folder 51/5)
    - Lansing B. Warner Incorporated, 1941 (Box-folder 51/6)
    - V, 1941 (Box-folder 51/7)
    - W, 1941 (Box-folder 51/8)
    - Y, 1941 (Box-folder 51/9)
    - Z, 1941 (Box-folder 51/10)
    - American Can Company, 1942 (Box-folder 51/11)
    - Association Seed Growers Incorporated, 1942 (Box-folder 51/12)
    - A, 1942 (Box-folder 51/13)
    - Bowler Brokerage Company, 1942 (Box-folder 51/14)
    - B, 1942 (Box-folder 51/15)
    - Calvert Lithographing Company, 1942 (Box-folder 52/1)
    - C, 1942 (Box-folder 52/2)
    - Douglas Guardian Warehouse Corporation, 1942 (Box-folder 52/3)
    - D, 1942 (Box-folder 52/4)
    - E, 1942 (Box-folder 52/5)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1942 (Box-folder 52/6)
    - F, 1942 (Box-folder 52/7)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1942 (Box-folder 52/8)
    - The Gerrard Company, 1942 (Box-folder 52/9)
    - George W. Goddard Company, 1942 (Box-folder 52/10)
    - Harold B. Godfrey, 1942 (Box-folder 52/11)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1942 (Box-folder 52/12)
    - G, 1942 (Box-folder 52/13)
    - H, 1942 (Box-folder 52/14)
    - I, 1942 (Box-folder 52/15)
    - Kelley-How-Thompson Company, 1942 (Box-folder 52/16)
    - Kieckheffer Container Company, 1942 (Box-folder 52/17)
    - K, 1942 (Box-folder 52/18)
    - James Q. Leavitt Company, 1942 (Box-folder 52/19)
    - L, 1942 (Box-folder 52/20)
    - Meinrath Brokerage, 1942 (Box-folder 53/1)
    - Montana, 1942 (Box-folder 53/2)
    - M, 1942 (Box-folder 53/3)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1942 (Box-folder 53/4)
    - National Canners Association, 1942 (Box-folder 53/5)
    - N, 1942 (Box-folder 53/6)
    - Eugene M. O'Neill, 1942 (Box-folder 53/7)
    - P, 1942 (Box-folder 53/8)
    - Ryan Wholesale Grocers, 1942 (Box-folder 53/9)
    - R, 1942 (Box-folder 53/10)
    - Safeway Stores, 1942 (Box-folder 53/11)
    - Olden Smith, 1942 (Box-folder 53/12)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1942 (Box-folder 53/13)
    - S, 1942 (Box-folder 53/14)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1942 (Box-folder 54/1)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1942 (Box-folder 54/2)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1942 (Box-folder 54/3)
    - T, 1942 (Box-folder 54/4)
    - United States, 1942 (Box-folder 54/5)
    - U.S. California and Chicago Quartermaster, 1942 (Box-folder 54/6)
    - U.S. Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1942 (Box-folder 55/1)
    - U.S. War Department, 1942 (Box-folder 55/2)
    - U.S. Printing and Lithograph Company, 1942 (Box-folder 55/3)
    - U, 1942 (Box-folder 55/4)
    - Lansing B. Warner Incorporated, 1942 (Box-folder 55/5)
    - W, 1942 (Box-folder 55/6)
    - Y, 1942 (Box-folder 55/7)
    - American Can Company, 1943 (Box-folder 55/8)
    - Association Seed Growers Incorporated, 1943 (Box-folder 55/9)
    - A, 1943 (Box-folder 55/10)
    - B, 1943 (Box-folder 55/11)
    - C, 1943 (Box-folder 55/12)
    - Darwin and Kenneth Curtis, 1943 (Box-folder 55/13)
    - Douglas-Guardian Warehouse Corporation, 1943 (Box-folder 55/14)
    - E, 1943 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1943 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - F, 1943 (Box-folder 56/3)
    - George W. Goddard Company, 1943 (Box-folder 56/4)
    - G, 1943 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - H, 1943 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - I, 1943 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - J, 1943 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - Kelley How Thompson Company, 1943 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Kieckhefer Container Company, 1943 (Box-folder 56/10)
    - K, 1943 (Box-folder 56/11)
    - J. C. LaRue, 1943 (Box-folder 56/12)
    - James Q. Leavitt, 1943 (Box-folder 56/13)
    - L, 1943 (Box-folder 56/14)
    - Meinrath Brokerage Company, 1943 (Box-folder 56/15)
    - Montana, 1943 (Box-folder 57/1)
    - M, 1943 (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1943 (Box-folder 57/3)
    - National Canners Association, 1943 (Box-folder 57/4)
    - N, 1943 (Box-folder 57/5)
    - P, 1943 (Box-folder 57/6)
    - R, 1943 (Box-folder 57/7)
    - Safeway Stores, 1943 (Box-folder 57/8)
    - Alden Smith, 1943 (Box-folder 57/9)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1943 (Box-folder 57/10)
    - S, 1943 (Box-folder 57/11)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1943 (Box-folder 57/12)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1943 (Box-folder 57/13)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1943 (Box-folder 58/1)
    - T, 1943 (Box-folder 58/2)
    - United States, 1943 (Box-folder 58/3)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1943 (Box-folder 58/4)
    - U.S. California Quartermaster Depot, 1943 (Box-folder 58/5)
    - U.S. Chicago Quartermaster Depot, 1943 (Box-folder 58/6)
    - U.S. Office of Price Administration, 1943 (Box-folder 58/7)
    - U.S. War Department, 1943 (Box-folder 58/8)
    - U.S. War Labor Board, 1943 (Box-folder 58/9)
    - U.S. War Production Board, 1943 (Box-folder 58/10)
    - U, 1943 (Box-folder 58/11)
    - V, 1943 (Box-folder 58/12)
    - Lansing B. Warner, 1943 (Box-folder 58/13)
    - W, 1943 (Box-folder 58/14)
    - Y, 1943 (Box-folder 58/15)
    - Z, 1943 (Box-folder 58/16)
    - American Can Company, 1944 (Box-folder 58/17)
    - Association Seed Growers Incorporated, 1944 (Box-folder 58/18)
    - A, 1944 (Box-folder 58/19)
    - B, 1944 (Box-folder 59/1)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1944 (Box-folder 59/2)
    - C, 1944 (Box-folder 59/3)
    - Douglas-Guardian Warehouse Corporation, 1944 (Box-folder 59/4)
    - D-E, 1944 (Box-folder 59/5)
    - Jay G. Feldstein Company, 1944 (Box-folder 59/6)
    - Food Industries Federation of Mutual Fire Insurance Company, 1944 (Box-folder 59/7)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1944 (Box-folder 59/8)
    - F, 1944 (Box-folder 59/9)
    - George W. Goddard Company, 1944 (Box-folder 59/10)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1944 (Box-folder 59/11)
    - G, 1944 (Box-folder 59/12)
    - Kelley How Thompson Company, 1944 (Box-folder 59/13)
    - Kieckhefer Container Company, 1944 (Box-folder 59/14)
    - H-K, 1944 (Box-folder 59/15)
    - James Q. Leavitt Company, 1944 (Box-folder 59/16)
    - L, 1944 (Box-folder 59/17)
    - Meinrath Brokerage Company, 1944 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - Missoula Mercantile Company, 1944 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - Montana, 1944 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - M, 1944 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - Nasch-Finch Company, 1944 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - National Canners Association, 1944 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - N-P, 1944 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - Ryan Groceries, 1944 (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Safeway Stores Incorporated, 1944 (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Alden Smith, 1944 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1944 (Box-folder 60/11)
    - R-S, 1944 (Box-folder 60/12)
    - George L. Tracy, 1944 (Box-folder 60/13)
    - George L. Tracy, 1944 (Box-folder 60/14)
    - United States, 1944 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1944 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - U.S. California Quartermaster Depot, 1944 (Box-folder 61/3)
    - Chicago Quartermaster Depot, 1944 (Box-folder 61/4)
    - U.S. National War Labor Board, 1944 (Box-folder 61/5)
    - U.S. Office of Quartermaster General, 1944 (Box-folder 61/6)
    - U.S. War Department Price Adjustment Board, 1944 (Box-folder 61/7)
    - U.S. War Food Administration, 1944 (Box-folder 61/8)
    - T-V, 1944 (Box-folder 61/9)
    - Lansing B. Warner, 1944 (Box-folder 61/10)
    - W, 1944 (Box-folder 61/11)
    - American Can Company, 1945 (Box-folder 61/12)
    - A, 1945 (Box-folder 61/13)
    - B, 1945 (Box-folder 61/14)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1945 (Box-folder 61/15)
    - C, 1945 (Box-folder 61/16)
    - Douglas Guardian Warehouse Corporation, 1945 (Box-folder 61/17)
    - D, 1945 (Box-folder 61/18)
    - E, 1945 (Box-folder 61/19)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1945 (Box-folder 61/20)
    - F, 1945 (Box-folder 61/21)
    - Gallatin Valley Seed Company, 1945 (Box-folder 62/1)
    - George W. Goddard Company, 1945 (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1945 (Box-folder 62/3)
    - G, 1945 (Box-folder 62/4)
    - H, 1945 (Box-folder 62/5)
    - I-K, 1945 (Box-folder 62/6)
    - L, 1945 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Montana, 1945 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - M, 1945 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - National Canners Association, 1945 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - N, 1945 (Box-folder 62/11)
    - R, 1945 (Box-folder 62/12)
    - S, 1945 (Box-folder 62/13)
    - T, 1945 (Box-folder 62/14)
    - United States, 1945 (Box-folder 62/15)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1945 (Box-folder 62/16)
    - U.S. Dept of War Food Administration, 1945 (Box-folder 62/17)
    - U.S. Quartermaster George R. Doran California, 1945 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - U.S. Depot Chicago, 1945 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - U.S. Office of Defense Transportation, 1945 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - U.S. Office of Price Administration, 1945 (Box-folder 63/4)
    - U.S. War Department, 1945 (Box-folder 63/5)
    - U.S. War Labor Board, 1945 (Box-folder 63/6)
    - U.S. War Production Board, 1945 (Box-folder 63/7)
    - U-Z, 1945 (Box-folder 63/8)
    - American Can Company, 1946 (Box-folder 63/9)
    - A, 1946 (Box-folder 63/10)
    - B, 1946 (Box-folder 63/11)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1946 (Box-folder 63/12)
    - C, 1946 (Box-folder 63/13)
    - D, 1946 (Box-folder 63/14)
    - E, 1946 (Box-folder 63/15)
    - Jay G. Feldstein, 1946 (Box-folder 63/16)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1946 (Box-folder 64/1)
    - F, 1946 (Box-folder 64/2)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1946 (Box-folder 64/3)
    - G, 1946 (Box-folder 64/4)
    - The Horsley Company, 1946 (Box-folder 64/5)
    - H, 1946 (Box-folder 64/6)
    - J, 1946 (Box-folder 64/7)
    - K, 1946 (Box-folder 64/8)
    - L, 1946 (Box-folder 64/9)
    - Meinrath Brokerage Company, 1946 (Box-folder 64/10)
    - Montana, 1946 (Box-folder 64/11)
    - M, 1946 (Box-folder 64/12)
    - N, 1946 (Box-folder 64/13)
    - O, 1946 (Box-folder 64/14)
    - P, 1946 (Box-folder 64/15)
    - R, 1946 (Box-folder 64/16)
    - Safeway Stores-Regent Can Food Company, 1946 (Box-folder 64/17)
    - Max O. Schmidt, 1946 (Box-folder 64/18)
    - Alden Smith, 1946 (Box-folder 64/19)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1946 (Box-folder 65/1)
    - S, 1946 (Box-folder 65/2)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1946 (Box-folder 65/3)
    - George L. Tracy Company, 1946 (Box-folder 65/4)
    - T, 1946 (Box-folder 65/5)
    - United States, 1946 (Box-folder 65/6)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1946 (Box-folder 65/7)
    - U.S. Army, 1946 (Box-folder 65/8)
    - U, 1946 (Box-folder 65/9)
    - V-Z, 1946 (Box-folder 65/10)
    - American Can Company, 1947 (Box-folder 65/11)
    - Ashley Mixon Canning Machinery Exchange, 1947 (Box-folder 65/12)
    - A, 1947 (Box-folder 65/13)
    - B, 1947 (Box-folder 66/1)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1947 (Box-folder 66/2)
    - C, 1947 (Box-folder 66/3)
    - D, 1947 (Box-folder 66/4)
    - E, 1947 (Box-folder 66/5)
    - Jay G. Feldstein Company, 1947 (Box-folder 66/6)
    - Food Industries Federation of Mutual Fire Insurance Company, 1947 (Box-folder 66/7)
    - Food Machinery Corporation, 1947 (Box-folder 66/8)
    - Food Processing Equipment Company, 1947 (Box-folder 66/9)
    - F, 1947 (Box-folder 66/10)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1947 (Box-folder 66/11)
    - G, 1947 (Box-folder 66/12)
    - H, 1947 (Box-folder 66/13)
    - I-J, 1947 (Box-folder 66/14)
    - K, 1947 (Box-folder 66/15)
    - James Q. Leavitt Company, 1947 (Box-folder 66/16)
    - L, 1947 (Box-folder 66/17)
    - Missoula Mercantile Company, 1947 (Box-folder 66/18)
    - Montana, 1947 (Box-folder 67/1)
    - M, 1947 (Box-folder 67/2)
    - N, 1947 (Box-folder 67/3)
    - O, 1947 (Box-folder 67/4)
    - P, 1947 (Box-folder 67/5)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1947 (Box-folder 67/6)
    - R, 1947 (Box-folder 67/7)
    - Alden Smith, 1947 (Box-folder 67/8)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1947 (Box-folder 67/9)
    - S, 1947 (Box-folder 67/10)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1947 (Box-folder 67/11)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1947 (Box-folder 67/12)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1947 (Box-folder 67/13)
    - T, 1947 (Box-folder 67/14)
    - United States, 1947 (Box-folder 67/15)
    - T-V, 1947 (Box-folder 68/1)
    - W, 1947 (Box-folder 68/2)
    - American Can Company, 1948 (Box-folder 68/3)
    - A, 1948 (Box-folder 68/4)
    - B, 1948 (Box-folder 68/5)
    - Calvert Lithographing Company, 1948 (Box-folder 68/6)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1948 (Box-folder 68/7)
    - C, 1948 (Box-folder 68/8)
    - D-E, 1948 (Box-folder 68/9)
    - Jay G. Feldstein Company, 1948 (Box-folder 68/10)
    - F, 1948 (Box-folder 68/11)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1948 (Box-folder 68/12)
    - G, 1948 (Box-folder 68/13)
    - H-I, 1948 (Box-folder 68/14)
    - J, 1948 (Box-folder 69/1)
    - K, 1948 (Box-folder 69/2)
    - L, 1948 (Box-folder 69/3)
    - B. W. Mann, 1948 (Box-folder 69/4)
    - Missoula Mercantile Company, 1948 (Box-folder 69/5)
    - Montana, 1948 (Box-folder 69/6)
    - Muirson Label Company, 1948 (Box-folder 69/7)
    - M, 1948 (Box-folder 69/8)
    - N, 1948 (Box-folder 69/9)
    - O, 1948 (Box-folder 69/10)
    - Product Advancement Corporation, 1948 (Box-folder 69/11)
    - P, 1948 (Box-folder 69/12)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1948 (Box-folder 69/13)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1948 (Box-folder 69/14)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1948 (Box-folder 69/15)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1948 (Box-folder 70/1)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1948 (Box-folder 70/2)
    - R-T, 1948 (Box-folder 70/3)
    - United States, 1948 (Box-folder 70/4)
    - U, 1948 (Box-folder 70/5)
    - V-Y, 1948 (Box-folder 70/6)
    - American Can Company, 1949 (Box-folder 70/7)
    - A, 1949 (Box-folder 70/8)
    - B, 1949 (Box-folder 70/9)
    - Kenneth Curtis, 1949 (Box-folder 70/10)
    - C, 1949 (Box-folder 70/11)
    - Elks, 1949 (Box-folder 70/12)
    - D-E, 1949 (Box-folder 71/1)
    - F, 1949 (Box-folder 71/2)
    - Callatin Valley Seed Company, 1949 (Box-folder 71/3)
    - Rollo Gullickson, 1949 (Box-folder 71/4)
    - G, 1949 (Box-folder 71/5)
    - H, 1949 (Box-folder 71/6)
    - I-K, 1949 (Box-folder 71/7)
    - James Q. Leavitt Company, 1949 (Box-folder 71/8)
    - L, 1949 (Box-folder 71/9)
    - B. W. Mann, 1949 (Box-folder 71/10)
    - Montana, 1949 (Box-folder 71/11)
    - M, 1949 (Box-folder 71/12)
    - N, 1949 (Box-folder 71/13)
    - O, 1949 (Box-folder 71/14)
    - P, 1949 (Box-folder 71/15)
    - Regent Can Food Company (Safeway Stores), 1949 (Box-folder 71/16)
    - R, 1949 (Box-folder 71/17)
    - Alden Smith, 1949 (Box-folder 72/1)
    - Stone Hall Company, 1949 (Box-folder 72/2)
    - S, 1949 (Box-folder 72/3)
    - George L. Tracy Company Billings, 1949 (Box-folder 72/4)
    - George L. Tracy Company Butte, 1949 (Box-folder 72/5)
    - George L. Tracy Company Great Falls, 1949 (Box-folder 72/6)
    - T, 1949 (Box-folder 72/7)
    - United States, 1949 (Box-folder 72/8)
    - U, 1949 (Box-folder 72/9)
    - V, 1949 (Box-folder 72/10)
    - W, 1949 (Box-folder 72/11)
    - Y, 1949 (Box-folder 72/12)
    - American Can Company, 1950 (Box-folder 72/13)
    - A, 1950 (Box-folder 72/14)
    - B, 1950 (Box-folder 72/15)